{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"29","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"35","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"72","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"15","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"24","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"15","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"36","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"35","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"54","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"27","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"80","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"28","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"31","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"17","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"64","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"80","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"36","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"23","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"19","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"24","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"54","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"11","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"11","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"27","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"48","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"19","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"30","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"35","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"72","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"11","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"36","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"72","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"50","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"11","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"45","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"56","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"27","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"70","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"80","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"30","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"30","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"15","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"28","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"30","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"70","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"48","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"24","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"11","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"32","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"70","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"17","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"36","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"28","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"23","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"27","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"70","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"40","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"70","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"28","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"36","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"19","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"30","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"100","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"19","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"36","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"50","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"24","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"24","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"49","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"60","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"56","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"25","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"64","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"49","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"64","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"32","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"11","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"50","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"80","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"35","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"36","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"63","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"100","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"17","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"70","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"28","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"35","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"64","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"17","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 4\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"40","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"13","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"64","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"100","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"100","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"56","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"22","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"32","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"64","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"15","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"56","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"31","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"50","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"28","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"17","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"21","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"32","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"64","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"50","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"13","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"35","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"32","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"30","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"24","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"32","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"31","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"49","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"50","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"70","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"100","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"81","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"14","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"70","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"17","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"18","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"32","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"50","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"15","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"28","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"45","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"15","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"15","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"16","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e10\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"37","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"63","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Целая часть?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e6\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"3","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"7","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e7\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e8\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e10\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e9\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"18","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"25","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"6","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"2\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"10","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"27","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e9\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e2\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : 1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"1","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"2","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"3\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e8\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"8","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"9","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e4\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"20","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e5\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e4\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"11","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"12","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"1\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e2\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e6\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e7\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"19","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"30","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
{"question":"\u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e3\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e5\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e : \u003csmall\u003e\u003csup\u003e1\u003c/sup\u003e\u0026frasl;\u003csub\u003e3\u003c/sub\u003e\u003c/small\u003e \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Целая часть?"},{"value":"4","hint":"Числитель?"},{"value":"5","hint":"Знаменатель?"}]}
